Guide to the Joy Golden Papers, 1956-2012 RL.00461
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Joy Golden papers
1956-2012
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Golden, Joy
RL.00461
28 Linear Feet
Advertising copy writer and executive for several American agencies, including BBDO, Normal Craig & Kummel, J. Walter Thompson (JWT), and Scali McCabe Sloves. Managed a radio advertising and production company, Joy Radio. The Joy Golden Papers span the years 1956-2012 and include correspondence, audition records, scripts, print advertisements, design layouts, storyboards, and other records that document Golden's career in print and radio/television broadcast advertising. Formats include audiocassettes, VHS and Umatic videotapes, 16mm and 1/4" reels, and DVDs. Companies represented include Batten, Barton, Durstine & Osborn (BBDO), J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT), Norman Craig & Kummel, Scali McCabe Sloves, and Golden's own company, Joy Radio. Client files include materials for Abe Beame for Mayor, Alpine Lace Cheese, Automated Data Processing (ADP), Blue Cross/Blue Shield of New Jersey, DuPont, E-Loan, Frommagerie Bel (Frobel), MTA, North Fork Bank, Port Authority of New York, Shell Oil, Warnaco and Wilmington Trust. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
10,000 Items
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
In addition, original audiovisual materials are closed to patron use. Research Services staff need to produce use copies before contents can be accessed.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Joy Golden Papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2012.
Biographical Note
Chronology List
1952-1956 BBDO, Copy Supervisor
1963-1965 Zakin Company, Vice President/Copy Chief
1965-1967 Johnstone, Vice President/Copy Chief
1967-1968 Kenyon & Eckhardt, Vice President/Group head
1968-1969 J. Walter Thompson Company, Vice President/Group head
1969-1972 DKG, Senior Vice President/Associate Creative Director
1972-1973 Daniel & Charles, Senior Vice President/Co-Creative Director
1973-1975 NCK, Senior Vice President/Co-Creative Director
1975-1978 Scali McCabe Sloves, Senior Vice President/Creative Group Head
1978-1980 Wells Rich Greene, Senior Vice President/Creative Group Head
1980-1984 Joy Golden Company, freelance creative service
1984-1985 TBWA
1985-2000 Joy Radio, Founder/CEO/Creative Director
Collection Overview
The Joy Golden Papers span the years 1956-2012 and include correspondence, audition records, scripts, print advertisements, design layouts, storyboards, and other records that document Golden's career in print and radio/television broadcast advertising. Formats include audiocassettes, VHS and Umatic videotapes, 16mm and 1/4" reels, and DVDs. Companies represented include Batten, Barton, Durstine & Osborn (BBDO), J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT), Norman Craig & Kummel, Scali McCabe Sloves, and Golden's own company, Joy Radio. Client files include materials for Abe Beame for Mayor, Alpine Lace Cheese, Automated Data Processing (ADP), Blue Cross/Blue Shield of New Jersey, DuPont, E-Loan, Frommagerie Bel (Frobel), MTA, North Fork Bank, Port Authority of New York, Shell Oil, Warnaco and Wilmington Trust.
Collection Arrangement
Organized into the following series: General Files; Account Files; Print Advertisements; Work Portfolio; Audiovisual Materials.
Related Material
Related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center collections:
Adrienne Cohen Papers
Bud Titsworth Commercials
J. Walter Thompson Company. Albert B. Stridsberg Papers
J. Walter Thompson Company. Carroll Carroll Papers
J. Walter Thompson Company. Jack Hilton Papers
J. Walter Thompson Company. John F. Devine Papers
J. Walter Thompson Company. Lois Gaeta Papers
J. Walter Thompson Company. Maury Holland Papers
Advertising -- History; Advertising; Videocassettes; Advertising agencies -- United States -- History; Radio scripts; Advertising agencies -- United States; Advertising agencies; Advertising -- United States -- History; Radio advertising; Advertising executives; Advertising executives -- United States; 16mm; Audiocassettes; Golden, Joy; Blue Cross and Blue Shield of New Jersey; Shell Oil Company; Port Authority of New York; New York (State) Metropolitan Transit Authority; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; Golden, Joy; Warnaco (Firm); Wilmington Trust Company; Beame, Abraham D. (Abraham David), 1906-2001; E.I. du Pont de Nemours & Company
- General Files, 1956-2012 and undated, 3 boxes
  - Articles and interviews, 1989 and undated (Box 1)
  - Articles and writings by Joy Golden, 1984-2010 (Box 1)
  - Article: Creative Secrets of Inspiration, 1985 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1989-1996, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Digital Items Removed forms, 2012 (Box 1)
  - Door to Door, 2006 (Box 1)
  - How It All Started, undated (Box 1)
  - Joy Radio awards list, 1983-1987 (Box 1)
  - Joy Radio case studies, undated (Box 1)
  - McCann Erickson Radio Co./Joy Radio partnership, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Photographs, 1960s-1980s and undated, 5 folders (Box 1)
  - Press clippings, 1985-1987, 3 folders (Box 1)
  - Press clippings, 1986-1990, 5 folders (Box 2)
  - Press kit materials, 1982-1992, 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Press kit materials, 1984-1992, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Press releases, 1980s and undated, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Printed material
    - Bob Guccione roast (25th anniversary of Penthouse Magazine), 1994 (Box 3)
    - DuPont: Constance Bannister's Babies and Yours Discuss Life in Carter's Knits of Orlon and Cotton, circa 1960 (Box 3)
    - DuPont: How to Make Your Figure Add Up with Proper Bras and Girdles, 1958 (Box 3)
    - Late in My Life (song), 1985 (Box 3)
    - Penick & Ford: Brer Rabbit Book of Molasses Magic, 1956 (Box 3)
    - Radio Coraggio (English and Italian), undated (Box 3)
    - Radio scripts, 1988-1999 (Box 3)
    - Radio workshop, 1986 (Box 3)
    - Writers' Guild of America: various publications on plagiarism, copyright, and WGA bylaws, 1983-1992 (Box 3)
  - Publicity, 1980s-1995 and undated, 3 folders (Box 3)
  - Recyclable copy, 1987-1994 (Box 3)
  - Reinvention, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Speech: Toronto, 1997 (Box 3)
- Account Files, 1953-2008 and undated
  - AAA/Connecticut Motor Club, 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - ABC/Ellen Burstyn Show, 1986 (Box 4)
  - Abe Beame for Mayor, 1968-1973, 4 folders (Box 4)
  - Absolut Vodka, 1999 (Box 4)
  - Ad Council/Radon PSA, 1990 (Box 4)
  - ADP (Automatic Data Processing), 1992-1993, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Agents and commissions, 1989-1990 (Box 4)
  - Alba Fit-n-Frosty, 1986 (Box 4)
  - Alcon, 1988-1989 (Box 4)
  - Allerest, 1990 (Box 4)
  - American Home Products/Preparation H, 1995 (Box 4)
  - American Inventors, 1991 (Box 4)
  - American Service Center/Lincoln-Mercury, 1988 (Box 4)
  - Adam & Eve Cranberry Juice, 2003 (Box 4)
  - Atlanta Marriott, 1985-1986 (Box 5)
  - Aunt Ruby's Garlic Spread, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Bauerlein Advertising, 1988-1990 (Box 5)
  - Beau Rivage, 1999 (Box 5)
  - Beber Silverstein, 1994 (Box 5)
  - Benihana, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Bison Light Chip Dip, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Blue Cross Blue Shield of N.J., 1992-1993, 5 folders (Box 5)
  - Boars Head, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Bristol Myers, new product presentation, 1980 (Box 5)
  - Café Crown, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Caldor, 1986 (Box 5)
  - Canada Dry, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Canadian Frost (John Ragger), 1985 (Box 5)
  - Care Choices HMO, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Carefree Sugarless Gum, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Casual Corner, 1992 (Box 5)
  - CBS/Beber Silverstein, 1988-1989 (Box 5)
  - Chanel product line strategies, 1975 (Box 5)
  - Channel Home Centers, 1991-1994 (Box 6)
  - Chapman/Easy Stamp, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Charles of the Ritz scripts, undated (Box 6)
  - Chase Manhattan, 1984 (Box 6)
  - Cheerwine, 1988-1989 (Box 6)
  - Chesebrough-Pond's: Time Balm advertising and marketing recommendation, 1969 (Box 6)
  - Chevrolet, 1989 (Box 6)
  - Choice Care HMO, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Citibank, 1985 (Box 6)
  - Clairol Color, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Close-Up Toothpaste, 1998 (Box 6)
  - Coca-Cola, 1988 (Box 6)
  - Cohen's Fashion Optical, 1987 (Box 6)
  - Columbus City Center, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Coors beer, 1989 (Box 6)
  - Crabtree & Evelyn, 1999, 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Cutter Insect Repellent, 1992-1993 (Box 6)
  - Daily Oklahoman, 1987 (Box 6)
  - Dairy Farmers of Washington, 1987 (Box 6)
  - Danskin, 1986 (Box 7)
  - Death Defying Acts (play), 1994 (Box 7)
  - Deloitte & Touche, 1996 (Box 7)
  - Delta Airlines, 1991-1994 (Box 7)
  - Dixan Detergent, 1986 (Box 7)
  - Don Buchwald & Associates, 1987 (Box 7)
  - Dot.Com, 2000 (Box 7)
  - Dunkin' Donuts, 1987-1994, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - DuPont: Let's Talk Sweaters, 1957 (Box 7)
  - E-Loan, 2001-2002, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Eight O'Clock Coffee, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Ellio's Pizza, 1988 (Box 7)
  - Empire Kosher Chicken, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Enterprise Rent-a-Car, 1991-1994, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Equitable Industrial, 1994 (Box 7)
  - Fair Insurance/Gold Direct, 1991-1992 (Box 7)
  - Fearon/First Investors, 1986 (Box 7)
  - FirstCom/Jim Long Companies, 1990 (Box 7)
  - First Florida Bank, 1989 (Box 8)
  - Fleischmann's Margarine, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Florida Gold Orange Juice, 1988 (Box 8)
  - Florida Power and Light, 1989 (Box 8)
  - Franklin Mint, 1987-1988 (Box 8)
  - Fresh Chef, 1989 (Box 8)
  - Frookies, 1989 (Box 8)
  - Frosty Paws, 1988-1994 (Box 8)
  - Gannett Newspapers, 1998 (Box 8)
  - GEICO, 1989 (Box 8)
  - General Tire, 1987 (Box 8)
  - Genie Garage Door Opener, 1988 (Box 8)
  - Gerald and Cullen Rapp, 1989-1990 (Box 8)
  - Golden Gateway, 2007 (Box 8)
  - Groark for Governor, 1994 (Box 8)
  - Group W/Mercury Awards, 1991-1992 (Box 8)
  - Haagen Dazs, 1992-1993 (Box 8)
  - Haircare Harmony, 1986-1987 (Box 9)
  - Hallmark, 1987 (Box 9)
  - Harman International, 1994 (Box 9)
  - Hertz rental cars, 1986 (Box 9)
  - Hughes Industrial/DirecWay, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Humane Society of South Lake Tahoe, 1987 (Box 9)
  - IC Beer, 1991 (Box 9)
  - Ice Breakers, 1996 (Box 9)
  - IKEA, 1994 (Box 9)
  - InterWest Bank, 1987 (Box 9)
  - JobsDirect.com, 2000 (Box 9)
  - Journal News, 1999 (Box 9)
  - KABC-TV, 1987 (Box 9)
  - KDKA-TV2, 1985 (Box 9)
  - KNBC-TV, 1991 (Box 9)
  - Konica, 1994-1995 (Box 9)
  - Korey Kay, 1999 (Box 9)
  - KYW-TV/Hunter television series, 1992 (Box 9)
  - La Prairie, 1986 (Box 9)
  - Ladies' Home Journal, 1986-1987 (Box 9)
  - Late Night Comic, 1987 (Box 9)
  - Lending Tree, 1999 (Box 9)
  - Lifesavers, 1993 (Box 9)
  - Lightpath, 2000-2003 (Box 9)
  - Lillet Wine, 1988 (Box 9)
  - Lipton Tea, 1992 (Box 9)
  - Live with Regis and Kathy Lee, 1991 (Box 10)
  - Love94/WLVE, 1988 (Box 10)
  - Lowe's Home Furnishings, 2001 (Box 10)
  - Magnum P.I. television series, 1986 (Box 10)
  - Mama Tish Italian Ices, undated (Box 10)
  - Marcus James, 1988 (Box 10)
  - MasterCard, 1989 (Box 10)
  - Mateus Wines, 1988-1990 (Box 10)
  - Maxwell House Coffee, 1985-1986 (Box 10)
  - McGavren Guild, 1985 (Box 10)
  - Medi-Quik, 1989 (Box 10)
  - Mercury Radio Awards, 1993 (Box 10)
  - Mirage Resorts, 1999 (Box 10)
  - Modell--Girl casting, 2005 (Box 10)
  - Moe Ginsburg, 1995 (Box 10)
  - Morgan Simpson, 1990 (Box 10)
  - MTA (Metropolitan Transit Authority)
    - Adam Sandler type voice, 2000 (Box 10)
    - Auditions, 1998-2000 (Box 10)
    - Casting, Security spot, 2005 (Box 10)
    - Christmas, 2001 (Box 10)
    - Convenience spot, 1999 (Box 10)
    - Grade Crossing spot, 2003 (Box 10)
    - Improvements, 2002 (Box 10)
    - Industrial, 2002 (Box 10)
    - Metro Card, 2002 (Box 10)
    - Miscellaneous, 2008 (Box 10)
    - Off-Peak/Weekend spot, 2001 (Box 10)
    - Once Upon a Time spot, 1998 (Box 10)
    - Spanish language spots, 2000-2002, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Two Santas, 2005 (Box 10)
  - Nabisco/Mr. Salty, 1994 (Box 10)
  - National Fuel, 1990 (Box 10)
  - Network America/Jerry Rubin, 1987 (Box 10)
  - New York Hospital, 1992-1994 (Box 10)
  - New York Institute of Technology (NYIT), 1999 (Box 11)
  - New York State Agricultural Board, 1992 (Box 11)
  - New York State/Catskills script, undated (Box 11)
  - Nike for Women, 1992 (Box 11)
  - Nivea, 1990 (Box 11)
  - Norseland Foods, 1994 (Box 11)
  - Nutrisystem, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
  - NYTEL, 1993 (Box 11)
  - Ohio Wines, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Old Tyme Soft Drinks, 1990 (Box 11)
  - Oxygen Media casting, 1999 (Box 11)
  - Patco, 1994 (Box 11)
  - Pedone/Sweet 'n Low, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Penguin's Frozen Yogurt, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Petrie Stores, 1993 (Box 11)
  - Pitney Bowes, 1987 (Box 11)
  - Pizza Hut Carryout, 1986 (Box 11)
  - Pizza Hut Lunch Pizza, 1986 (Box 11)
  - Port Authority, 2005-2006, 3 folders (Box 11)
  - Public Service of New Jersey, 1992 (Box 11)
  - Radio Advertising Bureau, 1986 (Box 11)
  - Ragu Foods, 1990 (Box 11)
  - Ralph Lauren, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Ralston Purina/Puppy Chow, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Rave Hair Products, 1998 (Box 11)
  - R.C. Willey's, 1989 (Box 11)
  - Republic National Bank, 1990 (Box 12)
  - Restaurant Association, 1989 (Box 12)
  - Rice Chex Juniors, 1989 (Box 12)
  - Rich's Southern BBQ, 1987 (Box 12)
  - Ringling Brothers Barnum & Bailey retail, 1991 (Box 12)
  - Riscassi & Davis, 1992, 2001 (Box 12)
  - Rivendell Psychiatric Centers, 1991 (Box 12)
  - Roy Rogers Restaurants, 1989 (Box 12)
  - Savings Bank of Manchester, 1994-1995 (Box 12)
  - Sharp, 1999 (Box 12)
  - Shoe Town, 1992 (Box 12)
  - Signal Mouthwash, 1986 (Box 12)
  - Sills & Co., 1986 (Box 12)
  - Smith Barney/Top Picks, 1999 (Box 12)
  - Smith's Market, 1993 (Box 12)
  - SOS soap pads, 1992 (Box 12)
  - Southern New England Telephone (SNET), 1985 (Box 12)
  - Sovran Bank, 1987 (Box 12)
  - Splash De-Icer (Factory Motor Parts), 2006 (Box 12)
  - Stella d'Oro, 1987 (Box 12)
  - Sterling Jewelers, 1988 (Box 12)
  - Stressbusters, 1985 (Box 12)
  - Subway Restaurants, 1994 (Box 12)
  - Sundance soft drinks, 1991 (Box 12)
  - TBS/The Chimp Channel, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Team Audio, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Tijuca Beer, 1986 (Box 13)
  - Tower Air, 1995 (Box 13)
  - Tower City Center, 1990 (Box 13)
  - Tri Star Pictures/Short Circuit II, 1988 (Box 13)
  - UDV Multibrands, 1998 (Box 13)
  - USA Network, 1987 (Box 13)
  - USA Print & Pop Ups, 1990 (Box 13)
  - U.S. Cellular casting, 2001 (Box 13)
  - V-8 Juice, 1988-1992 (Box 13)
  - Waldbaum's, 1992 (Box 13)
  - Waldenbooks, 1987-1988 (Box 13)
  - Wee Three Records, 1991 (Box 13)
  - Weight Watchers, 1991 (Box 13)
  - WFSB, 1988 (Box 13)
  - jWhitehall/Hoffman LaRoche cough syrup abuse PSA, 1990-1992 (Box 13)
  - Wiejske Wyroby Pickles/Milwaukee Pickles, 1993 (Box 13)
  - Wild Turkey, 1989 (Box 13)
  - Wilmington Trust, 1999-2002, 3 folders (Box 13)
  - WordPerfect, 1993 (Box 13)
  - WPIX-FM, 1985 (Box 13)
  - WRC Preview, 1990 (Box 13)
  - WRC-TV, 1991 (Box 13)
  - Zayre, 1986 (Box 13)
  - Zephyr Hills Spring Water, 1992 (Box 13)
- Print Advertisements, 1953-1980 and undated
  - Magazine
    - American Maple House, undated (Box 14)
    - Capital Cities Broadcasting, undated (Box 14)
    - Carter Products/Easy Day feminine spray deodorant, 1971 (Box 14)
    - Carter's children's clothing, 1950s (Box 14)
    - Coty/Élan perfume, undated (Box 14)
    - Dubl-Duck Sharper Blades, 1962 (Box 14)
    - Dupont Orlon, Nylon, 1953-1954 (Box 14)
    - Euphoria perfume, undated (Box 14)
    - Eve cigarettes, undated (Box 14)
    - Fleer Dubble-Bubble, 1964 (Box 14)
    - Gemex watches, 1954 (Box 14)
    - Herculon, undated (Box 14)
    - Maine Sardine Industry, 1954 (Box 14)
    - Oneida, 1960s (Box 14)
    - Quality Cosmetics/Monique, 1962-1963 (Box 14)
    - Security Hardware, 1962-1963 (Box 14)
    - Talon zipper, undated (Box 14)
    - Thomas More Book Club/U.S. Catholic, undated (Box 14)
    - Waring, 1964 and undated (Box 14)
    - Wella, 1962 (Box 14)
    - Wippette, undated (Box 14)
    - Yardley/Jaguar for men, undated (Box 14)
  - Newsprint
    - American Maple House, undated (Box 14)
  - Magazine
    - Chesebrough-Pond's, undated (Box 15)
    - Coty Originals, 1972 (Box 15)
    - Coty Ultra Legs, 1972 (Box 15)
    - Dictograph, 1962 (Box 15)
    - DuPont Nylon, 1954 and undated (Box 15)
    - Eve cigarettes, undated (Box 15)
    - Fieldcrest, 1979 (Box 15)
    - Fleer Dubble-Bubble, 1964 (Box 15)
    - McCall's, undated (Box 15)
    - Mennen, 1969 and undated (Box 15)
    - Monique/Thilene, 1962-1963 (Box 15)
    - Wella/Kolestral, 1962 (Box 15)
  - Newsprint
    - Abe Beame for Mayor, 1973 (Box 15)
    - Fleer Dubble-Bubble, 1963 (Box 15)
    - I Love New York, 1978 (Box 15)
    - New York Lottery, 1978 (Box 15)
    - Vogue, 1980 (Box 15)
    - Waring, 1964 (Box 15)
- Work Portfolios, 1969-1993 and undated
  - Awards, 1971-1993 (Box 16)
  - Coparel--Me! perfume launch, 1980 (Box 16)
  - Laminated advertisements, 1971-1979 and undated (Box 16)
    Scope and Contents note
    [Includes Bronx Zoo; Coty; Eve cigarettes; Finesse contraceptive gel; Fresh'n wipes; Max Factor; Sharon Christie Quickslim; Singer; Supp-Hose; Talon zipper; Vagisee douche]>
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 16)
  - Mom & Ollie: A treatment, undated (Box 16)
  - New Product Ideas for the Personal Products Company, 1980 (Box 16)
  - Small print advertisements, undated (Box 16)
    [Includes Emba minks; Finesse contraceptive gel; Remington appliances; Talon zipper; Vagisee douche]>
  - Speech: YWCA Academy of Women Achievers, undated (Box 16)
  - Awards, 1971-1993 (Box 17)
  - Print Advertisements
    - Air France, undated (Box 18)
    - Capital Cities Broadcasting PSA, undated (Box 18)
    - Chanel #19, undated (Box 18)
    - Charles Revson Ultima II, undated (Box 18)
    - Chesebrough-Pond's, 1969 (Box 18)
    - Coty, 1970-1979 (Box 18)
    - Easy Day Feminine Spray, undated (Box 18)
    - Emba Mink Breeders Association, undated (Box 18)
    - Eve cigarettes, undated (Box 18)
    - Hebrew National, undated (Box 18)
    - Max Factor, 1979 (Box 18)
    - People Resources, 1981 (Box 18)
    - Platinum industry, undated (Box 18)
    - Sperry Rand/Remington appliances, 1970 (Box 18)
    - Talon zipper, undated (Box 18)
    - Van Heusen, undated (Box 18)
    - Vogue Magazine, undated (Box 18)
    - Wippette, undated (Box 18)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1979-2005 and undated, 13 boxes
  - Audition tapes
    - ADP: Advisor. 1993. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV1)
    - ADP: Advisor/Helper. 1993. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV1)
    - ADP: Barney Krupp. 1992. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV1)
    - ADP: Helper. 1993. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV1)
    - ADP: Office Crisis. 1993. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV1)
    - Alcon/Optizyme: Born Again Buddhist. 1989Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV1)
    - Alpine Lace Cheese: Jewish Deli. 1991. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV1)
    - Alpine Lace Cheese: Korean Deli. 1991. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV1)
    - Alpine Lace Cheese: Pookins. 1991. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV1)
    - Alpine Lace Cheese: Pookins/Jewish Deli. 1994. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV1)
    - Arizona Daily Star: Valley Girl. 1986. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV1)
    - Benihana: Samurai; Coca-Cola: Tall Tale. 1990. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV1)
    - Blue Cross and Blue Shield of N.J.: Captain Crunch/King Lou. 1993. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV1)
    - Blue Cross and Blue Shield of N.J.: Mabel. 1992. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV1)
    - Blue Cross and Blue Shield of N.J.: Sue Frost/Lucky Doris. 1992. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV1)
    - Blue Cross and Blue Shield of N.J.: Sue Frost/Lucky Doris. 1992. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV1)
    - Blue Cross and Blue Shield of N.J.: Touched/Tina. 1991. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV1)
    - Blue Star Foods: Joan's Jewelry. 1986. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV1)
    - Blue Star Foods: Office Rendezvous. 1986. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV1)
    - Bryant Park: More Monty. 1988. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV1)
    - Burroughs Wellcome: HIV Testing. 1990. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV1)
    - Capalbo's Gift Baskets: Mr. Cheap/Bribe. 1995. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 6:00 (Box AV1)
    - Carlsberg: Shrink. 1992. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV1)
    - Carlsberg: Wedding/Living Together/Art Collector. 1987. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV1)
    - Casual Corner demo. 1992. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV1)
    - Catskills on Broadway: Doctor/Hello Lil/Messenger. 1992. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV1)
    - Chanel Home Centers: They Helped Me/Gift. 1991. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV1)
    - Cheerwine: Major Zero/Stars/Boring Dweeb. 1993. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV1)
    - Cutter Repellant: Tour. 1993. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV1)
    - Cutter Repellant: Tour/Wedding. 1992. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV1)
    - Empire Kosher Chicken: Uncle Morty. 1993. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV2)
    - Fair: Better Off Dead. 1991. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV2)
    - Family Counseling Services: Child Abuse. Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV2)
    - Frobel: Divorce. 1986. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV2)
    - Granada TV: Cheapskate. 1986. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV2)
    - Partnership for a Drug Free America: Where is the Baby?/Where is the Baby? Spanish/Dedicated to Wayne. 1989. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV2)
  - Compilations
    - Joy Radio (Frobel: Hot Tub Brunch/Sweet 16/Valley Girl; Jack Benny; Eagle Snacks: Anniversary). 1985. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 6:00 (Box AV2)
    - Joy Radio (Money Magazine: Dentist; Granada TV: Cheepskate/Dial-a-Deal; Goldstar: Grunitski/Low Class; Maxwell House: Sidewalk; S. New England Telephone: Sticky Stuff/Phoebe; Citibank: Appliance Store; Jefferson Bank: Gift). 1986. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV2)
    - Montage (Goldstar: Valet; Frobel: Hot Tub Brunch/Valley Girl/Red Jogging Hat; Eagle Snacks: Wacky Wacky; Granada TV: Cheapskate; Elephant Malt Liquor: Lawn Party; Hebrew National: Forgotten Salami; Carlsberg Beer: Art Collector; La Cage Aux Folles: Dear Jerry Herman; Pevely Dairy: Kezzy Boomer; Alpine Lace: Jewish Deli; WABC: Bad Connection; Jefferson Bank: Dr. Noodleman). 1995Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 3:25 (Box AV2)
    - Radio Advertising Bureau (I Saw It On The Radio: Big Bob's; Major Big; Sylvia; Al Popular; Ernest Trustworthy; Nobody Sees; Add Radio; Less TV; When They Shop; Sell Your Business; Full Bed Jingle; Jingle). 1988. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 9:00 (Box AV2)
  - Demos
    - Frobel Cheese/Laughing Cow (Arnold's Mom; Valley Girl; Sweet 16; Hot Tub Brunch; Holidays; Tailgate Party; Craving). Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 7:00 (Box AV2)
  - Music and Lyrics
    - Caesar's: N.Y. Loves Caesar's. Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV2)
    - Danskin music (David Spangler, Joy Golden). 1982. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV2)
    - Late in My Life (Joe Campodonico, Joy Golden). 1984. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV2)
    - Max Factor: Don't You Love Being a Woman (Jerry Alters, Joy Golden). Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV2)
    - Music Lyric reel. Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV2)
    - Visa: The Best of Life. Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV2)
  - Speeches